Fear is the new faith.
28 Years Later: The Bone Temple is a horror, thriller,
science fiction film directed by Nia DaCosta.
Kelson finds himself in a shocking new relationship - with consequences that could change the world as
they know it - and Spike's encounter with Jimmy Crystal becomes a nightmare he can't escape.
Dr. Ian Kelson, played by Ralph Fiennes.
Sir Lord Jimmy Crystal, played by Jack O'Connell.
Spike, played by Alfie Williams.
Jimmy Ink, played by Erin Kellyman.
Samson, played by Chi Lewis-Parry.
Jimmima, played by Emma Laird.
28 Years Later: The Bone Temple is a 2026 post-apocalyptic horror-drama
film directed by Nia DaCosta and written by Alex Garland.
It was shot back-to-back with its predecessor 28 Years Later (2025), and serves as
the fourth installment overall in the 28 Days Later film series.
The film stars Ralph Fiennes, Jack O'Connell, Alfie
Williams, Erin Kellyman, and Chi Lewis-Parry.
28 Years Later: The Bone Temple was released by Sony Pictures Releasing through its Columbia Pictures label in the United Kingdom on 13 January
2026, as part of a double bill with its predecessor, with the film being individually released the following day on 14 January.
It was released in the United States on 16 January 2026, and
received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film has grossed $46.1 million worldwide, making it
the second-highest-grossing film of 2026.
The film explores themes of england, post-apocalyptic
future, satanism, satanist, sequel.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.